Tokyo, Hong Kong, Singapore.
So the Indian leg of our
journey is finally upon us.
But, well, I'm a little bit worried.
I mean, is there anywhere
to get a cheeseburger there?
I've always heard India was a land
of curry, disease, too many people.
I know.
I'm worried my stomach won't be
able to handle the culture gap.
That assessment is rather distorted.
You needn't worry.
It's a country of extraordinary people.
That I assure you, my friends.
Well, we've reached Calcutta.
Let's get going.
Let me carry that for you.
Want a tattoo?
You're very pretty.
Need some antivenom?
It won't hurt your stomach.
Stay at our hotel.
Calcutta, India.
In the 20th century, its
population is 11 million.
Calcutta buzzes with a bustling energy
that will pull you in and never let you go.
I don't need any.
I'm sending some cow shit.
Seriously, thank you.
Oh, crap.
Somebody's already stolen my wallet.
Tip, tip, tip.
If you don't give me tips,
you won't go to heaven, sir.
Hey, kid, don't put your
nose all over my stuff.
Avdol, so this is India?
See?
Great country, isn't it?
They're what makes India
great, don't you think?
Thank you.
Yeah!
Here, try this.
This is chai.
I think you'll find it to your liking.
Chai, one of India's most popular drinks.
A sweet concoction made by boiling
black tea, sugar, and ginger with milk.
Ah, at last a little piece.
Be patient with India.
Once you get used to it, you'll
see how wonderful this country is.
You know, I kind of like this place.
It's pretty cool.
What, Jotaro?
You cannot be serious!
It's a hell of a lot of
culture shock, though.
Guess I'll like it once
I get used to it, huh?
Well, I guess people adapt to
their surroundings eventually.
Where's the John?
It's right over there, sir.
Polnareff! Yeah?
Aren't you going to order first?
Pick for me.
It better be something amazing.
Something gorgeous and sophisticated
that suits a Frenchman such as moi.
Which means it doesn't matter.
He'll eat anything.
Let's see.
What's something he'll like?
Excuse me.
Pardon me, sir.
Could you please wait?
Huh?
Please, use this while you're in here.
What am I supposed to do with this? Hey!
Ooh la la!
I must say,
the toilet looks weird, but at least
it's a lot cleaner than I had expected.
A gentleman like myself
has certain standards
and won't stand for it
when a bathroom is dirty.
Sir, is something wrong?
Don't!
Is something wrong me?
The toilet!
There's a pig sticking its head out of it!
Why, yes.
No need to be frightened.
He's actually quite friendly.
The builders constructed the pig pen down
below higher than they were supposed to.
So, when the pigs get hungry,
they come up for more.
That's all.
But that's not even what
I'm asking you about!
No, wait, what?
So you're telling me that
this pig's food is...
That's what it's there for?
As I told you, sir.
Here, use this stick.
Like this.
See, now you can do your business
while the pig's knocked down.
Though, some like the pig.
Our manager gets the pig to lick his
buttocks and always sings the pig's praises.
He gets it so clean.
Feel free to take your time.
Hey, monsieur!
Don't leave me alone!
I don't think I could ever get used
to this, no matter how much I tried.
I'll wait until we get to the hotel.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Oh, crap, the food.
Where is he?
No way.
Too weird.
I know I saw someone out there.
I must have imagined it.
I guess I can't help it.
I mean, there was a pig in
the john, for God's sake.
Oh, well, nothing there.
What's a little monster
in the mirror anyway?
So this is what they mean
by culture shock here.
What the hell
is going on here?
I can only see this damn
thing in the mirror.
This must be the mirror
stand Jotaro talked about.
Merde, this is not good.
Mon dieu, this is so not good.
THAT NEW MATERION!
Huh?
Where did that bastard go?
Damn it!
A stand! Huh?
But where's the user? Who is it?
The man with two right hands!
Too many people!
Damn it.
What's the matter, Polnareff?
What is this about?
If that was it,
If that stand belongs
to who I think it does,
then that means I finally found him.
Jotaro, the stand user who
uses the mirrors, he's here.
The bastard who killed my
sister, my angelic sister.
The scum who heartlessly
trampled my sister's life,
soul and pride who destroyed the world's
most pure heart finally finally we meet?
are you absolutely sure
it's him it's settled mr.
Joestar I'll be traveling on
My own from here on out with
my sister's murderer finally
within reach I'll be Damned
if I'm going to wait for him
to come after me I'm screwed
if he gets that drop on me
and that's just not my style.
I'll find him first and kill him!
But we don't even know what he
looks like or what his stand is.
He's got two right hands,
that's enough for me.
And don't forget, he knows
that I'm coming after him.
That should put him on the
defensive and give me the advantage.
See ya.
Tough talk for a man who's
digging his own grave.
And that means?
Just as it sounds, my friend.
Are you implying that I'm going to lose?
Yes.
Can't you see?
The enemy attacked in
order to isolate you.
He's exploiting your biggest weakness.
I won't let you go alone, Polnareff.
Listen up.
I'm only going to say it once.
This whole time, I never
once gave a damn about Dio.
I told you in Hong Kong that I would go
along with you so that
I could get my revenge.
Mr.
Joestar and Jotaro already know this.
Hmm, I've been alone from the beginning.
I've always been fighting alone.
You selfish fool!
Did you forget that you
were brainwashed by Dio?
Are you so foolish you forgot
that he's the root of all of this?
You have no idea how it feels to have
your sister murdered, so shut the hell up!
I heard the last time you met Dio,
you pissed yourself and ran away!
A coward like you would never
understand why I need to do this!
What did you say?
Don't touch me!
You just got lucky the day
you beat me in Hong Kong.
Enough with this lecturing!
How dare you?
Oh, did that offend you?
But don't forget,
I'm a lot angrier than you are right now
and with a hell of a lot better reason.
You can just keep being yourself with
your holier-than-thou attitude, Avdol.
Why, you...
Mr. Joestar!
That's enough.
Just let him go.
Now that his mind is made up, I
doubt that anybody could stop him.
Yeah, I've lost all respect
for him, that's all.
My impression of him was completely wrong.
You are correct in that I
did run in fear from him.
You see, I'm certain that
Foresight will let us win.
Rushing in without thinking
will get us killed. Oh?
Then I'll say this with certainty, too.
Your precious little
divination will be wrong.
Time to get off.
I'm here to see a friend of mine.
Now get gone, girl.
You're on your own.
Please make me your wife.
I'll do anything you want.
My life will belong to you.
Just say whatever you wish of me, my love.
Please let me stay with you.
Let me be by your side forever.
Oh, come on now.
Don't be stupid.
You're still only 16.
I'm old enough to marry.
I love you.
Listen, I'm just a no-good drifter, baby.
I live each day like it's my last, and
one day, the end will come for me. Shh.
This is no life for a lady,
and you have royal blood.
We can't have a fairytale marriage, no
matter how much we might love each other.
Really?
You've never said that before.
You love me? Yeah. Yeah.
You're the only woman I've ever loved.
That's just it.
It's because I love you
that we can't marry.
I want you to be happy
and have something better.
You understand, don't you?
I know, sweetheart.
This breaks my heart just
as much as it breaks yours.
But I'll come back to see you and
hold you like this whenever I can.
That's enough to make me happy.
Okay.
Goodbye, love you, darling.
You know it's bad manners to eavesdrop.
You think I spend too much
time on romance, don't you?
But when you've got girls like her all
over the world at your beck and call,
well, you've always
got an ally, a partner.
They'd do anything for me, even
throw away their own lives.
You are aware of how I work,
aren't you, Mr. Centerfold?
By the way,
about this Silver Chariot's Polnareff,
seems that he left the group and
is looking for you on his own.
What do you want to do he totally fell
for your plan hook line and sinker hmm?
Shall we go and kill him first!
Let's go you know between your
hangman and my emperor i have no doubt
that we can kill them all no sweat
this will be a hell of a ride!
So he really didn't come back after all.
What?
You've seen him?
Are you absolutely sure you
saw a man with two right hands?
Where?
I just saw him.
I don't understand it.
He was just right there.
There! What? There.
He was with that man in the street.
The gun is mightier than
the sword. Huh? Hmm.
Not bad, if I do say
so myself. Wait. What?
Who the hell are you, buddy?
Hmm.
Whole whores.
That's what they call me.
I'm a stand user, just like you are.
And my card is the emperor.
Lord Dio paid me to get rid of you guys,
so say your prayers and
get ready for a beating.
Look here, cowboy.
I don't give a rat's
ass who you say you are.
Where is the man with two right hands?
That was pretty rude.
You asked who I am, so I answered you.
Well, whatever.
I came here with that guy.
He's nearby. What?
Where is he?
There's really no point
at all in you asking that.
I, Whole Horse, will have the
pleasure of snuffing you out.
Arrogant morons like
you always talk trash,
and it always ends up
the other way around.
Oh, was that funny?
Lord Dio had you pegged.
Polnareff has the fatal habit of
underestimating his opponents.
Beating him into a corpse
won't be any trouble for you.
He was exactly right, so
I couldn't help but laugh.
If I can't face him until I defeat you,
then that's just what I'll do, chump.
Bring it on.
Ever heard of military chess?
The tank is stronger than the soldier,
and the tanks are weak against the mines.
See, it's pretty much
the basics of battle.
My emperor is stronger than you,
so I thought I'd be a gentleman.
I'll let you know my stand's abilities
before we fight, so we're square.
The gun is mightier than the sword.
Such a brilliant quote.
What are you trying to say exactly?
That I have a stand that shoots, and a
sword simply can't beat that. So what?
A pea shooter?
Prepare to die.
You underestimated me.
And now, Pawn O 'Ref, you're dead!
If I take off my armor, I
can knock down a bullet!
Wait, what the?
That's impossible!
It bypassed my sword!
Oh, crap!
The bullet is also my stand, and
underestimating me just cost you your life.
Please leave.
Polnareff!
What? Avdol!
I've been worried about you,
and now look where you are!
Your ego will end you, Polnareff!
You're worried about me? Damn you!
You came here to lecture me again?
The enemy already knows
everything about you!
You said you're a loner, but from now
on, you won't be able to win alone!
What bad timing for an
outsider to interfere.
Polnareff, move!
The bullet's coming back!
Go, Matryshids, run!
I'll melt it down!
Damn that, Avdol!
He went after Polnareff himself!
Where are you, Mr. Avdol?
Polnareff, I have a terrible feeling.
Hey, there's a weird
fight going on over there.
The plot hole!
What the?
Mr. Avgol!
Man, today must be my day. Hey!
My gun and centerfold's mirror don't do
very well against Avdol's flames, you see.
We were sure he'd be our
most formidable enemy.
Talk about luck!
With him gone, the game is in the bag.
Mr. Avdol!
He's just hurt, that's all.
It's just a minor wound, see?
He's going to start speaking.
He'll open his eyes in a moment.
Right, Mr. Avdol? Right?
You're going to wake up, right?
Mr.
Avdol, you've got to wake up!
No, please! Mr. Avdol!
That seemed awfully easy.
It was too quick.
That's what he gets for lecturing people.
Look at him now.
What did you say, Polnareff? Mr.
Avdol was worried about you.
Who asked him for help
because I never did?
He likes to meddle in
other people's business,
but he's slow as hell, so they got him.
Guys like him just get
in the way and screw up.
That's why I said I was going in alone.
You bastard.
He saved your life.
How dare you?
I am sick of it!
Having people up and die on me!
Polnareff...
I'm so sick of it!
You hear me?!
All the old paintings on the tomb.
They do the sand dance, don't you know?
If they move too quick, oh-way-oh!
They're falling down like a domino.
All the bars are men by the Nile.
They've got their money on a bet.
Called crocodiles.
They snap their teeth on your cigarette.
Falling types of the hookah. I say.
Walk
like
an Egyptian.
The blonde waitresses take their trays.
Spin around and they cross the floor.
They've got the moves.
You drop your drink then
they bring you more.
All the school kids so sick of books.
They're like the punk and the metal band.
When the buzzer rings.
They're walking like an Egyptian.
All the kids in the marketplace say.
Walk like an Egyptian.
For such a tough guy, he
sure was easy to finish off.
Come to think of it, that sweet sister
of yours was really good at sobbing.
You want me to hold these
regrets inside and run away?
Don't let him get to you, you're
much stronger than that Mr.
Avdol told you.
He begged you not to fight alone.